let MCQS = [{
    question: "What was Quentin Tarantino's first film?",
    choice1: "Pul fiction",
    choice2: "Resevoir Dogs",
    choice3: "From Dusk Til Dawn",
    choice4: "Jackie Brown",
    answer: 1
},
            {
            question: "What is the highest grossing film of all time?",
    choice1: "Titanic",
    choice2: "Frozen",
    choice3: "Avatar",
    choice4: "Avengers Endgame",
    answer: 2
},
            {
            question: "Which actor has never won an oscar?",
    choice1: "Matthew Mcconaughey",
    choice2: "Johnny Depp",
    choice3: "Sean Penn",
    choice4: "Gary Oldman",
    answer: 1
},
            {
            question: "Which actress has never won an oscar?",
    choice1: "Michelle Pfeiffer",
    choice2: "Emma Stone",
    choice3: "Cate Blanchette",
    choice4: "Sandra Bullock",
    answer: 0
},
            {
            question: "What is the biggest movie bombs",
    choice1: "The lone ranger",
    choice2: "The 13th warrior",
    choice3: "47 Ronnin",
    choice4: "R.I.P.D",
    answer: 1
},
            {
            question: "What is the most watched movie of all time?",
    choice1: "Lion King",
    choice2: "Terminator",
    choice3: "The Wizard of OZ",
    choice4: "Star Wars",
    answer: 2
},
            {
               question: "What was the first movie to feature a toilet flushing?",
    choice1: "Lawrence of Arabia",
    choice2: "Casablanca",
    choice3: "Gone with the wind",
    choice4: "Psycho",
    answer: 3
},{
               question: "In Bambi, what is the name of Bambis Skunk friend",
    choice1: "Skunk",
    choice2: "Smelly",
    choice3: "Flower",
    choice4: "Bob",
    answer: 2
},
            {
               question: "In Shrek, what does Shrek compare ogres to",
    choice1: "Apples",
    choice2: "Potatoes",
    choice3: "Onions",
    choice4: "Peaches",
    answer: 2
},
            {
               question: "In Forrest Gump, according to Forrest's mom what is life like?",
    choice1: "A box of choclates",
    choice2: "A shitshow",
    choice3: "A tough journey",
    choice4: "A loving journey",
    answer: 0
}];